export default [
  {
    question: "Fundamental blocks is know as  ?",
    options: ["Head", "Element", "HTML tag", "HTML attribute"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which parameter is used for size attribute ?",
    options: ["Inch", "Pixels", "Millimeter", "Cm"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "HTML tags are surrounded by which type of brackets ?",
    options: ["Round", "Angle", "Curly", "Squart"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "In how many ways can css be written in  ?",
    options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Four"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the following CSS property is used for controlling the layout  ?",
    options: ["Display", "Color", "Text", "None of the above"],
    answer: 0,
  },

  {
    question: "Which is not valid data type in Javascript?",
    options: ["Undefined", "Boolean", "Float", "Number"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "By which javascript code is used ?",
    options: ["Classes", "Methods/Functions", "RMI", "Events"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Everything in react is",
    options: ["Component", "Model", "Method", "Packge"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "React component can return how many components ?",
    options: ["One", "Two", "Three", "Multiple"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "React.js in MVC is ?",
    options: ["Model", "Middleware", "Method", "Controller"],
    answer: 3,
  },
];
